SHIVAM MORE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER
NASHIK, 422003, INDIA 7020093806

· DETAILS ·

Shivam bunglow,Uday colony,makhmalabad road Nashik, 422003 India 7020093806 shivamkm1692000@gmail.com

> Date of birth 16/09/2000

· LINKS ·

LinkedIn

· SKILLS ·

C++

SQL

Git

Python

JavaScript

React.js

Apache Spark

Azure

LANGUAGES

Marathi

Hindi

English

PROFILE

A creative thinker, Highly skilled software engineer with one year of experience seeking a challenging position to utilize my technical expertise and contribute to the development of innovative software solutions. I also like to make small indie games like escape room.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Intern at Persistent System, Pune

February 2022 - July 2022

- · Served as a dedicated and supportive Intern in a fast-paced environment.
- · Gained Knowledge about technologies like Nodejs ,React.

Software Engineer at Persistent Systems, Pune

July 2022 - Present

- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to gather requirements, design solutions and ensure timely project delivery.
- Participated in code reviews, identifying and resolving software defects and improving code quality.
- Assisted in the testing and debugging of software applications, ensuring optimal performance and functionality.
- Contributed to the documentation of software design, requirements and user
- Actively participated in Agile/Scrum meetings, providing updates on project progress and addressing any issues or blockers.

EDUCATION

10TH(SSC), St. Francis High School, Nashik (77.20)

June 2006 - May 2016

Diploma in Computer Technology, MVP RSM Polytechnic, Nashik (79.53)

August 2016 - April 2019

Degree in Computer Engineering, MET Institute Of Engineering, Nashik (Fourth Year SGPA: 9.45)

August 2019 - May 2022

★ PROJECT

Voice Control Car with Robotic Arm, Nashik

January 2019 - May 2019

In this project we have created a car attached with a robotic arm and camera which is controlled by voice and android app, we have use various technology and hardware like raspberry pi for processing ,Bluetooth adapter ,SD card for storing the program ,etc. This project was build to go at remote location and operate it by remotely for working.

Degree Project- Covid Detection System , Nashik

July 2021 - April 2022

In this project ,System checks 3 conditions whether the person is wearing mask or not, whether the temperature of the person is normal or not and whether the peoples are maintaining social distancing or not .If not the person will get email with body temperature and the photo and will advised to visit nearby hospital for checkup.